Seven hundred thirty-three adopters of the
Taskforce on Nature-related Financial
Disclosures. Twenty-two trillion dollars in
assets under management.
K-P-M-G's Survey of Sustainability Reporting:
biodiversity disclosure has doubled, but half
still don't report it.
GUARDIAN. Multi-agent biodiversity defense on
Google Cloud.
Camera-trap Tag twenty-two fires. Stream Watcher
confirms a vehicle. Audio Agent flags a gunshot,
point nine three confidence.
Species I-D grounds the herd against the
International Union for Conservation of Nature,
the Convention on International Trade in
Endangered Species, and the Taskforce on
Nature-related Financial Disclosures. Endangered.
Appendix One. Material.
The orchestrator fans out to four independent A2A
peers, each a separate service: Park Service.
Sponsor Sustainability. Funder Reporter. Neighbor
Park.
Anchored with a Secure Hash Algorithm
two-five-six signature. Tamper-evident audit
trail.
This filing I-D comes from a deterministic public
endpoint. Re-run the call and the same I-D comes
back. Source on GitHub.
Six Cloud Run services. One A-D-K orchestrator on
Gemini two point five Pro, plus the Ops Center
frontend. Four specialists. Four independent A2A
peers. Species I-D grounds against the
International Union for Conservation of Nature,
the Convention on International Trade in
Endangered Species, and the Taskforce on
Nature-related Financial Disclosures, via Vertex
AI Search. BigQuery audits the trail. Packaged
for Marketplace.
Fifty-eight trillion of Gross Domestic Product
depends on nature. The European Union's Corporate
Sustainability Reporting Directive requires
biodiversity disclosure under European
Sustainability Reporting Standards E-four.
GUARDIAN packaged for Google Cloud Marketplace,
the channels procurement already trusts.
Built by Omar Dominguez Mondragon. C-E-O and
Founder, GuardIAn Wildlife. M-I-T Sloan.